yourofferpro.com 2011-06-26

# Coolsavings

March 21, 2011

Our Commitment To Privacy

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use your personal information in connection with our advertising, content, e-commerce, promotional and service programs and other business activities (the "Program") and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services and the sites of our advertisers..

What Information We Collect 

When you visit our site we may collect two types of information: (a) personal information you actively choose to disclose and (b) information about you that is collected passively by our servers or obtained from third parties.

  * (a) Active Information. We collect information you actively choose to provide to us. By choosing to participate in our Program, you become a Member by disclosing the information on the registration page which may include: your email address, name, address, phone number and birth date. During the process of registering on our site, participating in various offers, completing surveys, or sending us emails or correspondence, we collect additional information that you may disclose to us, including for example mobile telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address), credit information, social security number, health information and personal preferences regarding lifestyle, products or services. 
  * (b) Passive Information. We may also collect passive information automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties. We collect some information about you simply by virtue of you connecting to our web site. Our servers automatically identify your computer by its internet protocol ("IP") address, a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. In addition, to participate in some of our programs a cookie may need to be active on your system. If you do not permit cookies you may not receive the benefits of our programs. Cookies are a feature of web browser software (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, etc.) that allows web servers to recognize which computer is used to access a web site. Cookies simplify subsequent interactions on our site and streamline your transactions on related web pages. Information collected through cookies may include the date and time of your visits, the site pages you viewed, the time spent at each page, and the web sites you visited just before and just after our site. You can disable the cookie function by following the instructions in the "help" section of your browser. However, doing so will likely make it not possible for our system to properly recognize you when you visit our sites, and consequently may make your participation in our program more difficult or not possible. In addition to the information you provide or that is collected automatically from our system, we may obtain information about you from our marketing partners or other third parties, and we combine that information with the information you actively provide or that is automatically collected by our servers. 

The term "Information" is used in this policy to refer to both types of information described above, as well as any Information that you provide to us directly by phone (including any phone number displayed via caller ID), text or SMS message, U.S. mail or through any other written or oral communication with us. 

How We Use And Share The Information Collected 

We use your Information to administer our business activities, provide customer services such as technical support, distribute information about changes to our site, and send you, and enable others to send you, information about products and services that may be of interest to you and to contact you or use your Information for any other marketing purpose. We send communications to you ourselves, and your Information also is shared with other organizations that may contact you for any marketing purpose by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication. 

OPT-IN NOTICE: By Participating, You Expressly "Opt In" To Receive Information And Grant Us Permission To Share Your Information

By signing up for our Program you expressly opt in to receive future information about products and services from us and from a variety of advertisers to whom we may provide your Information. (Information regarding opting out is described later in this policy.) Because you have opted in, we may share your personal information with third parties, including but not limited to our advertisers, BigRewards.com, ShoppingBag.com and HotSurveys.com (collectively Media Network, Inc.) for any reason we choose, including without limitation for the following purposes: (1) to operate our Program (including the transfer of the information to advertisers or to third parties who maintain on our behalf a list of persons having registered with our Program), (2) to permit advertisers or other third parties to use your Information for any purpose such as contacting you by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication for any purpose. As a result, we may transfer your Information to third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control.

In addition, in the event we consider a transaction involving the purchase or sale of our assets or stock, other companies may review our records, including your Information, to make business decisions about the transaction. Likewise, your Information may be transferred to third parties in the event of the sale or acquisition of our company or any of its assets. The parties who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant banks, our internet service provider, etc.) also may have access to your information in performing their services. 

Express Consent: By accepting the terms and conditions of this Site and providing your telephone number, you are subscribing to a service that transmits special offers to subscribers via pre-recorded voice messages. 

By subscribing, you are expressly consenting to receive pre-recorded telephone messages from The Firebrand Group, LLC, a Nevada company doing business as Worldwide Commerce Associates (“WCA”) that include special or discounted sales offers. You are subscribing to receive offers only from WCA, and only at the specific numbers(s) you have provided to us. Your consent will be effective regardless of whether the number you have provided: (a) is a home, business, or cell phone line; and/or (b) is or will be registered on any state or federal Do-Not-Call (DNC) list, and shall remain in effect until you revoke your consent and cancel your subscription. 

To unsubscribe: You may cancel your subscription and revoke your consent to receive pre-recorded telephone calls at any time by either (a) utilizing the opt-out procedure included in any message you receive; or (b) by calling 800-269-0281 

NOTE: WCA does not send offers via email, and is unable to honor any unsubscribe requests sent by other companies. If you are receiving offers via email please follow the unsubscribe instructions included therein. 

**Text messages:** By accepting the terms and conditions of this Site and providing your cell phone number, you are expressly consenting to receive SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone from us and other organizations. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove your information by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request. 

Special Note About Information You Provide Directly To Our Advertisers.

You are able to access certain advertiser's sites through our site. When you opt to receive information or sign up for an offer from an advertiser, you may be doing so through third party sites and with other companies over which we have no control. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you wish to opt out of those advertisers' mailings, you must do so directly with such advertisers or as otherwise provided on or through their sites. 

Third Party Ad Servers.

We may serve advertisements within our Web Site either ourselves or by allowing other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to do so. In addition, some of our advertisers may use the services of third-party ad networks. Some of these third-party ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the third-party ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, third-party ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows a third-party ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or third-party ad networks. Those third-party ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting. You may find more information at the web site of either the individual third-party ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative (http://www.networkadvertising.org), Privacy Choice (http://www.privacychoice.org/choose), and Digital Advertising Alliance (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

CoolSavings runs display banners provided by Advertising.com. To opt out of any beacon and/or cookie usage used for targeting associated with these banners, please go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

Security Of Your Information.

We use reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Information. However, nearly all Internet transmissions pass through many servers not controlled by us, and therefore we cannot guarantee that any information you provide us or we collect will not be intercepted or altered in that process. Also, as noted above, your Information is shared with third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control. 

How You Can Choose To "Opt Out" Of Receiving Further Information About Products Or Services

If at any time you do not wish to receive further information about products or services from us and wish us to cease providing your Information to third parties, you may choose to "opt-out" through the Unsubscribe/"Opt-Out" page of our site or by written request sent by U.S. mail to our Customer Service Manager at the following address:

CoolSavings Privacy, Q Interactive, Inc. One North Dearborn Street, 12th Floor Chicago, Illinois 60602 

We will promptly update our records upon receiving your clear instructions to opt-out, but it may take up to ten (10) business days from our receipt of your request for the change to be fully effective. If you later give us a clear statement that you want to receive emails from us or our advertisers after such date, then that opt-in statement will supersede any earlier opt-out request. If we have already provided your email address or other information to an advertiser or other third party before we receive your opt-out request, we cannot prevent them from sending or continuing to send you information or emails and you will need to contact such third party directly. 

How To Correct, Delete Or Access Your Information

If you wish to access, delete or correct the information you have provided to us through this site, please contact us through the Contact Us section of our site or through written request sent by U.S. mail to the Customer Service Manager at the address listed above..

Special Rights For Residents Of Certain States

If you are a California resident or another state with specific laws relating to the collection and use of Information, you may have specific rights not set forth in this policy. For example, California residents have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name registration (email address), the site name you visited and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please mail your request to Customer Service Manager at the address listed in the footer of this site or the Contact Us page.

PLEASE CHECK THIS PRIVACY POLICY PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES AS WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. SUCH REVISIONS TO THE PRIVACY POLICY SHALL TAKE EFFECT WHEN POSTED. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR SERVICES THROUGH ANY COMMUNICATION CHANNEL FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES.
